<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-US" /><updated>2022-03-10T00:24:27+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Cor3min3r’s Folio</title><subtitle>Hey Guys, it's me Cor3min3r. Pentester at Synack, Detectify, Bugcrowd, Intigriti and h1.  </subtitle><author><name>Cor3min3r</name><email>thehunterrico@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">MFA Bypass</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/MFA-Bypass/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MFA Bypass" /><published>2019-12-19T07:59:20+05:30</published><updated>2019-12-19T07:59:20+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/MFA-Bypass</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/MFA-Bypass/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/1*zu7qmgwwQ_SctNTJ0B6opA.jpeg" /></p>
<p>
Hello friends, this was my first writeup so please ignore my grammatical mistakes. Today I wanted to share you the way how I have bypassed MFA. Please read the bottom of the writeup where I have described what helped me to find out this bug. Let's get started
<p>
Before starting how I found the vulnerability, I'll give you some information regarding the target. I was invited to a private program so let say it as redacted.com. It had the functionality of maintaining all payment-related activities. So I started to test the application. I just started to sign-up for an account. While signing-up there was a page where you need to verify your phone number, We can't skip that verification. It was something like the below image.
<p>
<img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/1*ZQSemrgJfn3nXBApZw498Q.png" />
<p>
I entered my phone number and click on send code. And they sent an OTP to my number. I'm thinking of a way to bypass this authentication. I entered the wrong OTP in the OTP verification field and captured the request and the request of the POST data was something like this.{"id":"mph01SQXWUPMXTKTHzcj","token":"123456"}
<p>
I received an error message to enter the Correct-OTP. One thing got in my mind to check the response of the request. So I captured the response of the request and it was like the below image
<p>
<img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/1*_p6FP_ZGH7w_ks-OXoHWgA.png" />
<p>
I think you got it. Yah I modified the response.
<p>
And successfully I bypassed the MFA. I was like whooola..!
<p>
Special thanks to Udit Pratap Singh Bhadauria(Udit_thakkur)who motivated me to test the application because I wondered that even if I have found out a bug it will be anyhow going to duplicate as a large number of bugs have been reported already. Because of his motivation, I have found out this bug.
<p>
<b>Point to remember</b>: Dig deeper and deeper even a lot of bugs have been reported already, there will be something for you to find out.
<p>
<b>Bug Reported</b> : 31 Oct 2019 morning and they triaged by 31 Oct 2019 afternoon
<hr />
</p></p></p></p></p></p></p></p></p></p></p>]]></content><author><name>Cor3min3r</name><email>thehunterrico@gmail.com</email></author><category term="bugbounty" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello friends, this was my first writeup so please ignore my grammatical mistakes. Today I wanted to share you the way how I have bypassed MFA. Please read the bottom of the writeup where I have described what helped me to find out this bug. Let's get started Before starting how I found the vulnerability, I'll give you some information regarding the target. I was invited to a private program so let say it as redacted.com. It had the functionality of maintaining all payment-related activities. So I started to test the application. I just started to sign-up for an account. While signing-up there was a page where you need to verify your phone number, We can't skip that verification. It was something like the below image. I entered my phone number and click on send code. And they sent an OTP to my number. I'm thinking of a way to bypass this authentication. I entered the wrong OTP in the OTP verification field and captured the request and the request of the POST data was something like this.{"id":"mph01SQXWUPMXTKTHzcj","token":"123456"} I received an error message to enter the Correct-OTP. One thing got in my mind to check the response of the request. So I captured the response of the request and it was like the below image I think you got it. Yah I modified the response. And successfully I bypassed the MFA. I was like whooola..! Special thanks to Udit Pratap Singh Bhadauria(Udit_thakkur)who motivated me to test the application because I wondered that even if I have found out a bug it will be anyhow going to duplicate as a large number of bugs have been reported already. Because of his motivation, I have found out this bug. Point to remember: Dig deeper and deeper even a lot of bugs have been reported already, there will be something for you to find out. Bug Reported : 31 Oct 2019 morning and they triaged by 31 Oct 2019 afternoon]]></summary></entry></feed>